[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So we saw that deep learning had a tremendous part in the ImageNet
我们已经看到深度学习在ImageNet竞赛中
competition.
扮演了很重要的角色
Which allowed them to take 1.5 minute image string deeply on your network and
他们用1.5分钟 通过深度学习
get amazing performance to predict one of a thousand different categories.
来完美的在1000个类别中预测一张图片的类别
So let's go ahead and show you a little demo of what kind
今天我就来给你简单展示一下他们的成果
of categories we're talking about and how cool the predictions were.
来看看是哪写分类和预测的成功率如何
So here's an example.
让我们来看一个例子
It was the AlexNet frame on that ImageNet data set,
这是AlexNet 框架 用来预测ImageNet这个数据集
which we then employed as a service that can be queried from this website.
用来作为一个从网页上查询的服务器
And so every time I click on an image it gets sent to that service
每次我点击图片 其实它会传输到GPU
which actually runs on a GPU, so it's fast and it comes back for prediction.
这样会更快的计算 和返回预测结果
So if I click on this particular image here,
所以我点击了这张图片
it gets sent to a service that actually hosts in on Amazon AWS.
然后它把指令传输回在亚马逊网页服务上面的服务器
It comes back for prediction here.
然后返回预测
It's hidden, but when I click on it, it tells me what prediction is.
预测结果现在是隐藏的 当我点击了以后 他会告诉我预测结果是什么
So if I show you this image, it might be unclear what that image is, but
如果我给你看这张图片  也许这张图片不是很清晰
if I click on it, it says parking meter, it turns out to be the right label.
但是如果我点击了这张图片 它的预测是停车计时器 预测正确
The second best prediction was padlock, Which you can see kind of a padlock.
第二个备选的最佳预测是 密码锁 看上去有一点点像
The parking meter, you got it right.
但是停车计时器是正确的
So that's really quite cool.
所以说这个预测系统真的很厉害
Let me show you another example.
让我给你看另外一个例子
For example, this one.
比如说这个
It get shipped off to the service on Amazon WS, comes back for prediction.
也是同样传输回亚马逊网页服务器 然后进行预测
And here my prediction, screen, monitor, or [INAUDIBLE] it says it's a monitor, but
我的预测是 显示屏 显示器 就叫做显示屏好了
I don't know what the difference between a screen and a monitor is, but that's okay.
虽然我不知道显示屏和显示器的具体区别 但是无所谓了
So there's various images here, I'm just gonna click on a few.
还有很多很多图片 我就点几个看看
So for example, if I click on this one over here, it gets sent up.
如果我点这边的这个
It's really sure, it really thinks it's a spoonbill,
我觉得这是一个白琵鹭
it turns out to be a spoonbill, which is great.
这是一个白琵鹭 预测的也很对
Lastly I'm gonna click on this one over here and
然后我点这个
that image gets sent to that service uses a deep learning for GPU and
图片被发回了服务器 用GPU的深度学习
it says it's a beer bottle or pop bottle, the true label is beer bottle.
预测是啤酒瓶 正确的标签也是啤酒瓶
And now this all image is in the original ImageNet data set,
所有的图片都是来自于ImageNet 这个数据集
I'm sure an image that was not in
我很确定这张图片应该不在ImageNet这个数据集中
I click on this one here, it gets sent to that service.
我点了这个 然后它被发回到了服务器
On the AWS that we're hosting there.
继续发回到亚马逊网页服务器
Comes back for prediction, it says, Labrador retriever, this is my dog.
预测是拉布拉多巡回犬 这是我的狗狗
This is the lab in >> [LAUGH] And
这是这条狗的标签
this is the dog over here, in Dato.
就是这条狗啦
And so, as you can see, even for images that were not in the original data set,
你看到 即使对于很多不在ImageNet数据集中的图片
you can still get pretty interesting predictions.
我们还是能够做出很好的预测结果
Now in your capstone, you want to build a service now not for
在你的毕业设计项目中 你会建立起一个模型
predicting images here but for recommendations with deep learning, for
不是用来预测图片 还是用深度学习做推荐系统
product images and text and host it as a service.
推荐产品图片和文本 然后建立起一个服务器
And you'll be able to get a website like this, that anybody can play with, use, and
然后你就能得到一个像这样的网页 然后任何人都能使用
really see the power of the machine learning that you've been learning about.
你就能看到机器学习的用处和魅力了
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community